nomorehotels.com 2002-08-02

# NoMoreHotels Homestays vacation rentals short term rentals timeshares condos apartments villas bungalows homes

|    
| **General** | At No More Hotels, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit No More Hotels on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet. If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need to correspond with you, or provide you with a subscription, for example, it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it. 

* * *  
  
---|---  
**Listings** | By adding a listing on No More Hotels, the owner or property manager implies agreement to our [disclaimer](http://www.nomorehotels.com/disclaimer.htm).  
In order for listings on No More Hotels to receive email inquiries, through the site, a full and accurate email address must be given.  
Email addresses of parties whose properties are listed on No More Hotels are not disclosed on the site at any time for protection against unsolicited email from third parties. Email addresses associated with listings on No More Hotels remain unknown to the correspondent(s) until the owner/manager of the associated listing responds directly to the correspondent(s). 

* * *  
  
**Accuracy** | We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personal information. We have implemented appropriate procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner. 

* * *  
  
**Cookies** | Cookies can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Most often a cookie is simply a serial number that is generated so that your session on the website will remain uninterrupted. Some No More Hotels pages may use cookies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You will be notified if ever there is an occasion when the acceptance of cookies is necessary for reliable use of No More Hotels.
